https://www.cushiontheimpact.co.uk/privacy-policy/

You are here: Home » Privacy PolicyLast Updated 12 May 2018Introduction1.1     cushion the impact is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.1.2   We are registered as a data controller with the UK Information Commissioner’s Office. Our data protection registration number is Z4871001.1.3   This website is owned and operated by cushion the impact ltd.1.4   We are registered in England and Wales under registration number 040001331 and our principal place of business and registered office is at 27 Old Gloucester Street, London, WC1N 3AX. Our postal address is 2 Angel Square, London, EC1V 1NY.1.5   You can contact us by writing to the postal address given above, by using our website contact form, by email to info@cushiontheimpact.co.uk or by telephone on 020 3218 0053.1.6   If you are not happy with any aspect of how we collect and use your data, you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We should be grateful if you would contact us first if you do have a complaint so that we can try to resolve it for you. Collecting personal information2.1     We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths);information you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our newsletters and blog (including your name and email address);information relating to any purchases you make of our goods and/or services (including your name, address, telephone number, email address and card details);information that you post to our website for publication on the internet (including your user name, your profile pictures and the content of your posts);information contained in or relating to any communications that you send to us or send through our website (including [the communication content and meta data associated with the communication).2.2     Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must obtain that person’s consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in accordance with the terms of this policy.2.3     We do not collect any Sensitive Data about you. Sensitive data refers to data that includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data. We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offences. Using your personal information3.1     Personal information submitted to us through our website will be used for the purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the website.3.2     We may use your personal information to:(a)     administer our website and business;(b)     personalise our website for you;(c)     enable your use of the services available on our website;(d)     send you goods purchased through our website;(e)     supply to you services purchased through our website;(f)      send statements, invoices and payment reminders to you, and collect payments from you;(g)     send you non-marketing commercial communications;(h)     send you email notifications that you have specifically requested;(i)      send you our email newsletter, if you have requested it (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require the newsletter);(j)      keep our website secure and prevent fraud;(k)     verify compliance with the terms and conditions governing the use of our website (including monitoring private messages sent through our website private messaging service).3.3     We will not, without your express consent, supply your personal information to any third party for the purpose of their or any other third party’s direct marketing.3.4     All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services providers Eventbrite or PayPal. You can review the provider’s privacy policy at https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/privacypolicy/ https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full . We will share information with our payment services provider only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. Disclosing personal information4.1     We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.4.2     We may disclose your personal information:(a)     to the extent that we are required to do so by law;(b)     in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;(c)     in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);(d)     to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.4.3     Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information to third parties. We require all third parties to whom we transfer your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We only allow such third parties to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions. Retaining personal information5.1     This Section 5 sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal information.5.2     Personal information that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.5.3     Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 5, we will retain documents (including electronic documents) containing personal data:(a)     to the extent that we are required to do so by law;(b)     if we believe that the documents may be relevant to any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings; and(c)     in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk). Security of your personal information6.1     We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.6.2     We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall-protected) servers.6.3     You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. Amendments7.1     We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.7.2     You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy. Your rights8.1     You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you; provision of such information will be subject to you supplying appropriate evidence of your identity.8.2     We may withhold personal information that you request to the extent permitted by law.8.3     You may instruct us at any time not to process your personal information for marketing purposes.8.4     In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes. Third party websites9.1     Our website includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party websites.9.2     We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies and practices of third parties. Updating information10.1  It is very important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. Please let us know if at any time your personal information changes by emailing us at info@cushiontheimpact.co.uk Cookies11.1   Our website uses cookies.  A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.11.2   Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.11.3   Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.11.4   The names of the cookies that we use on our website, and the purposes for which they are used, are set out below:(a)     we use Google Analytics on our website to  analyse the use of the website. Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), to help us see how our website is used. In doing so information about your use of our website, including your IP address, may be transmitted to Google and stored on servers. The data collected by Google Analytics is used to analyse how frequently the same people revisit the our website, how the website is found (from advertising or referring websites), and which pages are most frequently viewed. This information is combined with data from thousands of other users to create an overall picture of website use, and is never identified individually or personally and is not linked to any other information we store about you.NamePurposeExpires_gaThis helps us count how many people visit our site by tracking if you have visited before2 years_utmaLike _ga, this lets us know if you’ve visited before, so we can count how many of our visitors are new to our site or to a certain page2 years_utmbThis works with _utmc to calculate the average length of time you spend on our site30 minutes_utmcThis works with _utmb to calculate when you close your browserwhen you close your browser_utmzThis tells us how you reached our site (like from another website or a search engine)6 monthsanalytics_nextpage_callThis lets us know the next page you visit on our site, so we can make journeys betterwhen you close your browserGDS_successEvents and GDS_analyticsTokensThese help us identify how you use our site so we can make the site better4 months11.5   Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.11.6   Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites. If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.11.7   You can delete cookies already stored on your computer. Deleting cookies will have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
